dandad.org 2005-03-06

# D&AD: Terms and conditions of the Design And Art Direction

Except where indicated otherwise all copyright and other rights that subsist in the home page and in the sub-domain pages of the www.dandad.org website ("the Site") are owned by British Design & Art Direction of 9 Graphite Square, Vauxhall Walk, London SE11 5EE (“D&AD”). 

The use of all pages of the Site are subject to the following terms and conditions of use but access to certain pages of the Site, some of which may be restricted, may be subject to further conditions of use as indicated: 

1\. You may browse, download, view, print and copy onto the hard disk of your computer [(but not photocopy)] any material from the Site for your own personal use only. Any other type of use requires the prior written agreement of D&AD. 

2\. The Site is intended to be accessed by users in the UK. Non-UK users must appreciate that the information contained on the Site may not be relevant to them and that their access to the Site might be restricted by local laws. 

3\. You will not use the Site: 

(a) for the posting, uploading, emailing or other transmission of any material, the publication, dissemination, use or possession of which infringes the rights of any person or which is unlawful in any other respect; 

(b) in any way which is abusive, defamatory or obscene or which will harass, distress or inconvenience any person or which might restrict or inhibit the use and enjoyment of the Site by any person; 

(c) for the posting, uploading, emailing or other transmission of any unsolicited or unauthorised advertising, promotional materials, "junk mail," "spam," "chain letters," "pyramid schemes," or any other form of solicitation or commercial exploitation; 

(d) for the posting, uploading, emailing or other transmission of any material that contains software viruses or any other computer code, files or programs designed to interrupt, restrict, destroy, limit the functionality of or compromise the integrity of any computer software or hardware or telecommunications equipment; 

(e) [to create a commercial database (electronic or otherwise) that includes material downloaded or otherwise obtained from the Site;] 

(f) [to transmit or re-circulate any material obtained from the Site to any third party;] 

(g) in such a way so as to remove the copyright or trade mark notice(s) from any copies of any material made in accordance with these terms; or 

(h) in any way that might bring D&AD into disrepute. 

4\. Whilst every effort has been taken to ensure the accuracy of the information provided by D&AD, its employees and agents in these pages, the contents of the Site are naturally subject to change from time to time. D&AD cannot guarantee the accuracy or completeness of all information on the Site. YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR CHECKING THE ACCURACY OF RELEVANT FACTS AND OPINIONS GIVEN ON THE SITE BEFORE ENTERING INTO ANY COMMITMENT BASED UPON THEM. 

5\. D&AD cannot guarantee that your use of the Site will be free from error and/or uninterrupted. D&AD, its [directors], [its trustees], its employees and its representatives exclude, in so far as it is legally possible, all liability and responsibility for any damages (other than liability for death or physical injury arising out of the negligence of D&AD or its officers) including, but not limited to, indirect or consequential damages, damages for loss of opportunity or chance, or any damages whatsoever arising from use or loss of use, data, or profits, whether in action of contract, negligence or other action, arising out of, or in connection with, any information on the Site or any other Internet sites or the use thereof. 

6\. Where information (including sensitive financial or personal information) is provided to D&AD directly through the Site or by email you accept that these methods of communication cannot be 100% secure. [D&AD uses encryption software to attempt to prevent unauthorised access to this information being obtained. However, ]D&AD cannot accept any responsibility or liability for any damages (other than liability for death or physical injury arising out of the negligence of D&AD or its officers) arising from the misuse or loss of data or information submitted by you to D&AD directly through the Site or by email. 

7\. Some of the pages on the Site include links to external websites. These links are included to give you the opportunity to access other pages that it is felt may be of interest or assistance to you. D&AD is not responsible for the content of these Internet sites. 

8\. Whilst effort has been taken to ensure that the Site is free from viruses, D&AD gives no warranties it will always be free from viruses and you are responsible for ensuring that you have installed adequate and up-to-date virus-checking software. D&AD excludes, in so far as it is legally possible, all liability and responsibility (other than liability for death or physical injury arising out of the negligence of D&AD or its officers) for any viruses or any other computer code, files or programs designed to interrupt, restrict, destroy, limit the functionality of or compromise the integrity of any computer software or hardware or telecommunications equipment or other material transmitted with or as part of the Site. 

9\. The names, images and logos identifying D&AD or third parties and their products and services, are the proprietary marks of D&AD, and/or may be the proprietary marks of third parties. Any use made of these marks may be an infringement of rights in those marks and D&AD reserves all rights to enforce such rights that it might have. 

10\. These terms may be varied from time to time. Please ensure that you review these terms and conditions regularly as you will be deemed to have accepted a variation if you continue to use the Site after any variation has been posted. 

11\. If any of these terms and conditions should be determined to be illegal, invalid or otherwise unenforceable, it shall be severed and deleted from the terms and conditions and the remaining terms and conditions shall survive, remain in full force and effect and continue to be binding and enforceable. 

12\. These terms and conditions shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of England and Wales. Any disputes arising from matters relating to the Site shall be exclusively subject to the jurisdiction of the courts of England and Wales. 

####  **Privacy Statement**

At D&AD, we take your privacy seriously. 

**Introduction**  
1\. This website is owned and operated by British Design & Art Direction (D&AD). All references to 'our', 'us' or 'we' within this policy are deemed to refer to D&AD. 

2\. We are committed to protecting your personal privacy. We provide this privacy policy to help you to understand how we collect information through this website and what we may do with any information that we obtain from you. 

3\. We may need to update this privacy policy from time to time so we recommend that you check you have read the most recent policy when you visit our website. 

**General**  
1\. D&AD respects the right to privacy of every individual who visits our website. This Privacy Policy outlines the information we collect that is Personally Identifiable Information, how we use and store the information collected, and your rights to verify and amend the information. 

2\. By using this website, and providing us with information, you consent to its use in line with this policy. D&AD will always handle information in compliance with the Data Protection Act (1998). 

**Information that we Collect when you Provide It**   
At various points throughout the site, we may ask you to provide information so that we can provide services to you. The information is collected and used as follows: 

1\. If you register with us, we collect your name, contact details and information on your company. This information is used by us to contact you about D&AD’s activities. 

2\. If you choose to receive further information from us, we will keep you informed of future D&AD activities. 

3\. If you choose to receive information from third parties, your contact information may be used by carefully selected complimentary organisations to inform you of offers or events. 

4\. When you contact us using the "Contact Us" form on the site, we collect your name, email address and any comments that you provide. This information is used by us to respond to your comments. 

**Other Information that we Collect**   
When you visit the site, we log the IP address of the machine you used to access our site with. The IP address is a unique number that is used on the Internet to identify a unique computer for the purposes of allowing computers to communicate with each other. 

Certain features of our site require Cookies in order to function. A Cookie is a small piece of information that is placed on your computer, and is used to differentiate you from other users accessing our site. We use this so that we can ensure your information is kept separate from that of other users of the site. For more information on cookies, please refer to the documentation provided with your web browser software. 

We may also collect information on the type of web browser that you are using, the operating system that your computer uses, and (where applicable) the link that you followed to get to our website. We use this information to produce general statistics about the numbers of unique visitors to the site and what software they use. In turn, these statistics are used to channel effort into further developing our site to meet the needs of our users. 

**Security**  
D&AD takes the security of any information we hold very seriously, and will always implement security measures that are in line with, or exceed current best practices and recommendations. 

Where necessary, and in common with other websites, we use SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encryption to ensure that information provided to us is not visible to anybody else when in transit between your computer and our servers. You can tell when SSL is in use by the presence of a small "padlock" symbol in the status bar of your web browser. 

In addition, our web servers are housed behind a secure firewall that prevents access to our databases from unauthorised users. All of our servers are housed in a secure environment with high levels of physical security, and access is only permitted to a handful of security screened staff. 

**Amendments to Data**   
For the purposes of the Data Protection Act (1998), the controller of all information collected on this website is: 

British Design & Art Direction  
9 Graphite Square  
Vauxhall Walk  
London  
SE11 5EE 

If you wish to view, delete or amend any of the information we hold on you, this can be done by contacting us through the web site, or by writing to us at the address provided above. We will not charge for amending or deleting personal information, but may charge for viewing information held on you as specified in the Data Protection Act (1998). 

**Children (under 18's)**  
We encourage parents and guardians to supervise the use of the Internet by their children, and to educate them about providing personal information both on the Internet and elsewhere. 

Where we expect children under the age of 18 to make use of a facility on our website, then we will display a notice stating that parental consent should be given before providing us with any information. 

Information provided by those under 18 may be deleted or removed through the website, or by the parent or guardian writing to us at the address given in the section "Amendments to Data". 

**Third Parties**  
D&AD does not and will never pass your information to any third party without your prior authorisation. Where information is collected on our behalf by third parties (such as for the purposes of surveys), we will ensure that they comply with our policy as outlined in this document. 

**Direct Marketing**  
D&AD will only ever contact you with marketing information where you have requested to receive it. If at any time you do not wish to receive such information, then you may ask us to amend our records appropriately (see section on Amendments to Data). 

**Further Information**  
If you require further information or have any questions regarding this policy, then please email us on [privacy@dandad.co.uk](mailto:privacy@dandad.co.uk).
